<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TUTYSARA&#39;S SPACE</title>
    <link>http://www.tutysara.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TUTYSARA&#39;S SPACE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <managingEditor>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 tutysara</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 19:17:21 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.tutysara.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix isset error in Hugo 2 version</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2017/03/26/fix-isset-error-in-hugo-2-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 19:17:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2017/03/26/fix-isset-error-in-hugo-2-version/</guid>
      <description>I have setup automatic compiling and deploying of my blog using Travis.CI
Recently I encountered a strange issue, the blog compiles and runs fine in my system but the site doesn&amp;rsquo;t come up after a Travis build.
On investigation found this in the logs from Travis CI.
Deploying updates to GitHub... Started building sites ... ERROR 2017/03/25 02:31:30 .Page&#39;s Use RSSlink is deprecated and will be removed in Hugo 0.21. RSSLink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacemacs Ctrl-i fix </title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2017/03/24/spacemacs-ctrl-i-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 09:07:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2017/03/24/spacemacs-ctrl-i-fix/</guid>
      <description>Spacemacs uses Ctlr+o to move backward to the last edited location and Ctrl+i to move foward after going back using Ctrl+o similar to Vim.
I found that Ctrl+o works but Ctrl+i doesn&amp;rsquo;t moves forward through the edit locations. I had the same issue in OSX/emacs 25.1 and in ubuntu/emacs25.1.
Searched the net and found this helpful issue page &amp;ndash; https://github.com/syl20bnr/spacemacs/issues/5050
We have the troubleshooting steps there
(lookup-key evil-motion-state-map [C-i]) ;; should be evil-jump-forward (display-graphic-p) ;; should be t dotspacemacs-distinguish-gui-tab ;; should be t (lookup-key key-translation-map [?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create custom profile ID in googleplus</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/29/how-to-create-custom-profile-id-in-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 04:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/29/how-to-create-custom-profile-id-in-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>I was writing my blog and added a link to google plus in the sidebar. I wanted to make a human readable/rememberable Id to use for my google plus page.
I guess, planning to {use|add link} to google plus is a bad idea. I googled to find the steps to create a custom profile Id and landed in the documentation page &amp;ndash; Get a custom URL for your Google+ profile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating hugo blog deployment to github pages using travis-ci</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/27/automating-hugo-blog-deployment-to-github-pages-using-travis-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 03:35:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/27/automating-hugo-blog-deployment-to-github-pages-using-travis-ci/</guid>
      <description>Here are the steps I took to build and deploy my blog automatically using hugo and travis-ci to github pages
I assume a hugo blog is already created and exist
 Create .travis.yml file in the project directory with the following contents
language: go sudo: required git: submodules: true install: - go get -v github.com/spf13/hugo script: bash ./deploy.sh notifications: email: on_failure: always  Generate and encrypt github token
 create a access token in github as given here , this is for pushing the changes to the master branch of the user site install travis gem</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Font for Spacemacs</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/03/good-font-for-spacemacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2016/09/03/good-font-for-spacemacs/</guid>
      <description>Spacemacs recommends using source code pro as the default font, infact this is the font set in .spacemacs file. If the font is not availale it is substituted for some other alternative. To find the font in use do C-u C-x = on my mac it was using Menlo font. DejavuSansMono looks better than Source code Pro on ubuntu and I switched to it in my ubuntu system. A list of top programming fonts can be found at Top programming fonts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django development on OSX using emacs</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/30/django-development-on-osx-using-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/30/django-development-on-osx-using-emacs/</guid>
      <description>I started following the Django tutorials by arun. I wanted to know about the related classes and quickly look into docs for the things that I code, I wanted an environment that is nice to newbies, helping with code completion and easy documentation lookup. I searched and found a huge list of options. Since I was begining with Django I wanted an environment that is much easier to setup, my first choice was pycharm, but unfortunately the community edition of pycharm doesn&amp;rsquo;t support Django - see this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a Hacker news clone</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/21/running-a-hacker-news-clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/21/running-a-hacker-news-clone/</guid>
      <description>I very much like the presentation of hackernews when it comes to understanding and making sense of the discussions quickly. It is a lot easier than reading pages of forums to get the main ideas of the discussions since the top comments and active discussions bubble to the top.
I wanted to run a site for discussing and sharing information that are useful for people working in techparks and the format that immediately clicked in my mind was the hacknews style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a  new VPS server</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/18/setting-up-a--new-vps-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/18/setting-up-a--new-vps-server/</guid>
      <description>These are the things I did to setup new VPS instances on Digital Ocean and ChicagoVPS
Update the machine sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get upgrade  Set locales sudo locale-gen sudo dpkg-reconfigure locales  add user sudo adduser tutysra # give sudo previliges sudo visudo tutysra ALL=(ALL) ALL  Install Git sudo apt-get install git  Install sun java sudo add-apt-repository ppa:webupd8team/java sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install oracle-java7-installer  Install Tor for screen scrapping sudo apt-get install tor sudo /etc/init.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correlation between INR values of different currencies</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2012/10/05/correlation-between-inr-values-of-different-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2012/10/05/correlation-between-inr-values-of-different-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Correlation between INR values of different currencies 2012-09-05 11:31  data clojure     This is an interesting take away example from the class which Anand is teaching at NIAS. Here we are trying to correlate between the INR values of various currencies like AUD, CNY (Chinese Yen), EUR, GBP (Great Britain Pound), JPY, SGD, USD and find the positive or negative correlations. The focus is on data collection and transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started blogging from a new place</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2012/09/02/started-blogging-from-a-new-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2012/09/02/started-blogging-from-a-new-place/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking about having a professional looking blog/space for some time. I noticed many people I follow on github maintaining a neat blog, I see that many of them use jekyll/ octopress and use github pages for hosting. I like the concept of static blogging and wanted to give it a try. 
  I gone through the process and it looks neat and clean, create a github repo with your username and drop html pages into it and github takes care of serving them, damm simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/about/</guid>
      <description>  I am Saravana, a programmer doing entreprise software by day and hacking on interesting stuff by night. I Love to try new things and experiment with various technologies/things that interests me. I usually find that my interest keeps changing and centered mostly around making things easy for me.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara att google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/contact/</guid>
      <description>tutysara -&amp;gt; at -&amp;gt; g mail. com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>