<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on TUTYSARA&#39;S SPACE</title>
    <link>http://www.tutysara.net/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on TUTYSARA&#39;S SPACE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <managingEditor>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 tutysara</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.tutysara.net/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Flashcards from Twitter -- Part1 Data Collection and Preprocessing</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/02/09/machine-learning-flashcards-from-twitter----part1-data-collection-and-preprocessing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/02/09/machine-learning-flashcards-from-twitter----part1-data-collection-and-preprocessing/</guid>
      <description>I was searching the net for mlflashcards, I found this incredible machine learning flashcard tweet series from Chris Albon. It looks pretty and covers a lot of ground, Got a thought &amp;ndash; why not download them for later use? I thought it would be a fun exercise to start the weekend and jumped into action.
Step 1 &amp;ndash; Collect/Scrape data from twitter I evaluated using twitter api using tweetpy, but it has its own limitation aka we can search only a week worth of data which is not good for our use case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Themes and Extensions for Jupyter notebook</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/02/07/themes-and-extensions-for-jupyter-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/02/07/themes-and-extensions-for-jupyter-notebook/</guid>
      <description>I am taking the wonderful fast.ai (http://course.fast.ai/) course thought by Jermey Howard and Rachel. We use jupyter notebooks in classes and it is always nice to see how Jermey&amp;rsquo;s notebook looks.
It has few tweaks like
 collapsible headings better tables and fonts  Learnt that he uses a themes for the visual customizations and an extensions to allow collapsing of headers from his reply in forums (http://forums.fast.ai/t/collapsable-expandable-jupyter-cells/205/5)
The theme script can be installed from this github repo (https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Skipgrams with sklearn CountVectorizer and TfidfVectorizer</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/01/07/use-skipgrams-with-sklearn-countvectorizer-and-tfidfvectorizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2018/01/07/use-skipgrams-with-sklearn-countvectorizer-and-tfidfvectorizer/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t have an implementation for skipgrams in sklearn. This post covers how to use the skipgram function in nltk with sklearn&amp;rsquo;s CountVectorizer and TfidfVectorizer
We are going to create a skipgram tokenizer that can be passed to the tokenizer parameter of the vectorizer.
Create a basic tokenizer that can split the original strings to tokesn. Tokenizer can be just .split() or a function to filter non-alpahbets etc. We can use tokenizer as below</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django development on OSX using emacs</title>
      <link>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/30/django-development-on-osx-using-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tutysara at google mail.com (tutysara)</author>
      <guid>http://www.tutysara.net/posts/2013/10/30/django-development-on-osx-using-emacs/</guid>
      <description>I started following the Django tutorials by arun. I wanted to know about the related classes and quickly look into docs for the things that I code, I wanted an environment that is nice to newbies, helping with code completion and easy documentation lookup. I searched and found a huge list of options. Since I was begining with Django I wanted an environment that is much easier to setup, my first choice was pycharm, but unfortunately the community edition of pycharm doesn&amp;rsquo;t support Django - see this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>